<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on The Scrum DAO</title>
    <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on The Scrum DAO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:49:35 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/table-of-contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:49:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/table-of-contents/</guid>
      <description> Table of Contents  Overview  Concept Integrations Main Scenario  QuickStart Project Structure  Oracle Project Contract PlanningPoker Contract ProductBacklog Contract Crowdsale Contract   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:52:19 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/overview/</guid>
      <description>Concept The Scrum DAO it&amp;#39;s an attempt to combine flexible software development methodology (Scrum) and Decentralized Autonomous Organizations (DAO).
We also want to offer a new approach to ICO to prevent over-inflating budget and greater involvement of investors in the development process. The idea is very simple - emit new tokens when some portion of work has been done and approved. The project capitalisation grows smoothly in parallel with features implementation and investors doesn&amp;rsquo;t pay just for hype</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 21:16:17 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/quick-start/</guid>
      <description> QuickStart </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 21:17:54 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/structure/</guid>
      <description>Project Structure Main Scenario  Project Owner deploys contracts and adds Workers. When Issue created in the PM TrustedOracle(not Owner) push new votings to ProductBacklog and PlanningPoker Contracts. Any token Holders can vote for issue&amp;rsquo;s priority in the ProductBacklog. Workers play in a PlanningPoker and vote for issue&amp;rsquo;s story points. When Issue closed Worker get an award which depends on issue&amp;rsquo;s story points. Worker put sell order in the Crowdsale contract.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>