<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Scrum DAO</title>
    <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Scrum DAO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:49:35 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/table-of-contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:49:35 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/table-of-contents/</guid>
      <description> Table of Contents  References Problem Statement  Pump and Dump Schemes The ICO Bubble Lack of Investor Participation  Our Solution  Concept The Scrum DAO Ecosystem Smart Contracts Protocol  Project Contract PlanningPoker Contract ProductBacklog Contract Crowdsale Contract   Applications  An alternative to ICOs Development of open source projects The distribution of shares among founders Rewarding employees  Conclusion  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:52:19 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/references/</guid>
      <description> References  scrumdao.com - Live demo Jira board - Join our development Telegram chat - Join discussion devorchestra.io - Our team&amp;rsquo;s website  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:52:19 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/overview/</guid>
      <description>Problem Statement It is true that in 2017, ICOs have become the chief crowdfunding means of choice for many startups. Many entrepreneurs instead of going through the many regulatory bottlenecks associated with IPOs and other mainstream venture capital activities now seem to prefer to go via the ICO route. Developers are introducing business models and concepts almost on a daily basis in order to take advantage of the popularity of the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 20:52:19 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/solution/</guid>
      <description>Our Solution With the number of ICO failures that have been recorded and the many faults inherent in the system, it is clearly apparent that an alternative approach is needed. The Scrum DAO offers an elegant and effective alternative to ICOs by combining our flexible software development methodology with a well-structured DAO framework.
Concept In the Scrum DAO, all the stakeholders in the development process are brought together under one entity which allows for greater interaction between investors and developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 21:17:54 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/applications/</guid>
      <description>Applications There are a number of potential applications of the Scrum DAO concept. These applications include:
An alternative to ICOs ICOs have created the false narrative that millions of dollars in crowdfunding is required to successfully implement a project. There are however numerous open source projects that exist and grow without the need for an unnecessary influx of investor funding.
By implementing and incentivized and collaborator project development framework, the Scrum DAO is better able to get investors to become involved in the development process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/conclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 21:16:17 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devorchestra.github.io/the-scrum-dao-site/post/conclusion/</guid>
      <description>Conclusion In terms of the roadmap, the Scrum DAO has no rigidly predetermined roadmap. After the beta release, the power to decide the features to be developed next will be delegated to the community. Members wishing to vote on issues can visit our backlog which can be found here. Members can also add new issues to the backlog. Some of the features that we are interested in developing are as follows:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>